let arr = [
  {"id":366,"question":"The GROUP BY command cannot be used with aggregate functions together","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":179,"question":"Containers running on a single machine all share the same operating system kernel.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":675,"question":"What is a Binary file","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Regular file","answer_b":"Directory","answer_c":"System file","answer_d":"Executable file","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":98,"question":"Can echo in PHP accept more than 1 parameter?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":965,"question":"Kubelet is a?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A node agent that manages pods and their containers","answer_b":"A smaller version of Kubernetes","answer_c":"Software that is used to run containers outside of pods","answer_d":"A device that collects data in an organized manner for easy access","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":79,"question":"In PHP, the only way to output text is with echo.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":300,"question":"What is the difference between character 23 and x23?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"23 specifies the octal 23 and x23 determine the hex 23.","answer_b":"23 specifies the hex 23 and x23 determine the octal 23","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":580,"question":"What is Joomla in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Set of library enriched with fucntions","answer_b":"Framework for designing dynamic pages","answer_c":"An open source CMS","answer_d":"framework and distribution system for reusable PHP components","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":134,"question":"Inline elements are normally displayed without starting a new line","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":368,"question":"MySQL supports user defined functions","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1008,"question":"When started for the first time, minikube requires Internet access. True or False?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":394,"question":"To use MySQL on your computer, you'll need","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Perl, PHP Or Java","answer_b":"FTP And Telnet","answer_c":"Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases","answer_d":"A Browser","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1019,"question":"Is Kubernetes open-source?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":180,"question":"Docker can build images automatically by reading the instructions from:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker.config","answer_b":"docker.json","answer_c":"docker.yaml","answer_d":"Dockerfile","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":63,"question":"The PHP syntax is most similar to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"JavaScript","answer_b":"Perl and C","answer_c":"VBScript","answer_d":"Bash","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":985,"question":"How can you add a comment in a JavaScript?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/\/This is a comment","answer_b":"'This is a comment","answer_c":"<!--This is a comment-->","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1075,"question":"In which file, can we permanently change the SWAP priority","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/etc\/fstab","answer_b":"\/etc\/prswap","answer_c":"\/etc\/swappriority","answer_d":"\/etc\/boot.conf","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":543,"question":"What is cite tag in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<cite title\"value\">Some Text Here<\/cite>","answer_b":"<cite title:\"value\">Some Text Here<\/cite>","answer_c":"<cite title=\"value\">Some Text Here<\/cite>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":116,"question":"Which of the following is used to declare a constant","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"const","answer_b":"define","answer_c":"constant","answer_d":"def","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1026,"question":"What is Docker Swarm mode?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A swarm is the name of the latest Docker release","answer_b":"A swarm is a group of machines that are running Docker and joined into a cluster","answer_c":"Docker swarm is also known as Docker Hub","answer_d":"Docker swarm is a tool for managing your CI\/CD pipelines","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":135,"question":"How can you make a numbered list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<ol>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<list>","answer_d":"<ul>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":958,"question":"In Kubernetes, a node is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A tool for starting a kubernetes cluster on a local machine","answer_b":"A worker machine","answer_c":"A machine that coordinates the scheduling and management of application containers on the cluster","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":859,"question":"How to copy a file from a docker container to the local system.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ sudo docker cp","answer_b":"$ sudo docker cut","answer_c":"$ sudo docker copy","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":209,"question":"UPDATE keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"to create database elements","answer_b":"to change data","answer_c":"to manage users","answer_d":"to select data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":129,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element to define emphasized text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<i>","answer_b":"<em>","answer_c":"<italic>","answer_d":"<it>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":961,"question":"In the context of Kubernetes, what is a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"An application which requires dedicated hardware to run on","answer_b":"A container is a standard unit of software that packages up code and all its dependencies so the application runs quickly and reliably from one computing environment to another","answer_c":"A large metal box that is used to hold or transport something","answer_d":"A unit that stores data on a computer's memory drive","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":162,"question":"Which HTML element is used to specify a header for a document or section?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<top>","answer_b":"<header>","answer_c":"<head>","answer_d":"<section>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1022,"question":"Which command will you use to pull a Docker image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker get IMAGE_NAME","answer_b":"docker image-pull IMAGE_NAME","answer_c":"docker pull IMAGE_NAME","answer_d":"docker start IMAGE_NAME","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":340,"question":"Who developed WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress was co-founded by Allen Mullenweg and Luke Little on the 27th of June 2003.","answer_b":"WordPress was co-founded by Matt Mullenweg and Mike Little on the 27th of May 2003.","answer_c":"WordPress was co-founded by Andrew Mclean and Mike Hathaway on the 24th of May 2003.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":443,"question":"What is the HTML Tag for the largest heading","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<h6>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<heading>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1019,"question":"Is Kubernetes open-source?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":219,"question":"What does SQL stands for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Structure query language","answer_b":"Strong question language","answer_c":"Structured question language","answer_d":"Separate query language","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":146,"question":"Which HTML element defines the title of a document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<title>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<meta>","answer_d":"<start>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":705,"question":"Deployment Controllers are part of","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Master Controller Manager","answer_b":"kube-scheduler","answer_c":"etcd manager","answer_d":"API Controller Manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"A Deployment provides declarative updates for Pods and ReplicaSets.You describe a desired state in a Deployment, and the Deployment Controller changes the actual state to the desired state at a controlled rate. You can define Deployments to create new ReplicaSets, or to remove existing Deployments and adopt all their resources with new Deployments.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":720,"question":"Cronjobs in kubernetes run in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UTC only","answer_b":"Based on NTP settings","answer_c":"Master node local timezone","answer_d":"GMT only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":21,"question":"Which of the following is a text editor that can be used in command mode to edit files on a Linux system?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"vi or vim","answer_b":"lsof","answer_c":"open","answer_d":"edit","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":214,"question":"What does the WHERE SQL operator does:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"restricts the set of rows to the selection of those records for which the condition is true","answer_b":"converts the value of a column or function to a different type","answer_c":"changes the order of output rows","answer_d":"eliminates all row repeats from the result set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":908,"question":"__________________ is responsible for health check of the pods running on individual nodes","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kubectl","answer_b":"Kubelet","answer_c":"Kube scheduler","answer_d":"Kube controller manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":647,"question":"Which command can be used to count characters in a text file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ccount","answer_b":"fsize","answer_c":"count","answer_d":"wc","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":644,"question":"How can you set the default rwx permission to all users on every file which is created in the current shell?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"umask  0777","answer_b":"chmod  777","answer_c":"chown  777","answer_d":"umask  0666","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"bash","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":492,"question":"Which of the following tags represents a section of the document intended for navigation in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"footer","answer_b":"dialog","answer_c":"section","answer_d":"nav","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":98,"question":"Can echo in PHP accept more than 1 parameter?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":140,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a text area?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"textbox\">","answer_b":"<textarea>","answer_c":"<input type=\"textarea\">","answer_d":"<textbox>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":1041,"question":"What language is an Ansible playbooks are written in by default?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"YAML format","answer_b":"JSON format","answer_c":"XML format","answer_d":"HTML format","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":324,"question":"You have lost access to your admin area and can't recover it with email. What do you do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Delete your themes folder.","answer_b":"Reinstall Wordpress.","answer_c":"Install a plugin to recover your password.","answer_d":"Add a new user with admin privileges in MySQL.","answer_e":"Reset the password of your user through MySQL.","answer_f":"Register a new user and set it as an administrator via your panel."},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":892,"question":"What are the components of Docker architecture?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The components of a Docker architecture are the Server, client, and Images.","answer_b":"The components of a Docker architecture are the host, client, and registry.","answer_c":"The components of a Docker architecture are the Services, Auth, and Prod.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":179,"question":"Containers running on a single machine all share the same operating system kernel.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":740,"question":"How to stream pod logs (stdout) in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl logs -f my-pod","answer_b":"kubectl pod -f my-pod","answer_c":"kubectl stream -f my-pod","answer_d":"kubectl logs my-pod","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":16,"question":"Which command is used to create new directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"dir","answer_b":"newdir","answer_c":"mkdir","answer_d":"cdir","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1046,"question":"Which command will you use to test the connectivity to the host from the master server and make sure that it actually works?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ansible your_host_name_here -m pong","answer_b":"ansible your_host_name_here -m connect","answer_c":"ansible your_host_name_here -m try","answer_d":"ansible your_host_name_here -m ping","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":340,"question":"Who developed WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress was co-founded by Allen Mullenweg and Luke Little on the 27th of June 2003.","answer_b":"WordPress was co-founded by Matt Mullenweg and Mike Little on the 27th of May 2003.","answer_c":"WordPress was co-founded by Andrew Mclean and Mike Hathaway on the 24th of May 2003.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":991,"question":"JavaScript is the same as Java.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":116,"question":"Which of the following is used to declare a constant","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"const","answer_b":"define","answer_c":"constant","answer_d":"def","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":319,"question":"What can the Contributor role do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Publish Posts","answer_b":"Edit Pages","answer_c":"Edit Posts","answer_d":"Moderate Comments","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":852,"question":"How to stop a container with container id mentioned in the command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker ter 109cb6nw","answer_b":"$ docker stop -ls 109cb6nw","answer_c":"$ docker stop 109cb6nw","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":956,"question":"How to remove two pods labelled 'production' and 'development'","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ kubectl delete pods -l 'env in (production, development)'","answer_b":"$ kubectl trim pods -l 'env in (production, development)'","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":961,"question":"In the context of Kubernetes, what is a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"An application which requires dedicated hardware to run on","answer_b":"A container is a standard unit of software that packages up code and all its dependencies so the application runs quickly and reliably from one computing environment to another","answer_c":"A large metal box that is used to hold or transport something","answer_d":"A unit that stores data on a computer's memory drive","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":620,"question":"What is the difference between mysqli_fetch_object() and mysqli_fetch_array()?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The mysqli_fetch_object() function collects the first single matching record where mysqli_fetch_array() collects all matching records from the table in an array.","answer_b":"The mysqli_fetch_object() function collects all matching records from the table in an array where mysqli_fetch_array() collects the first single matching record","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":390,"question":"MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SHOW;  ;","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"CHARACTER SET;","answer_d":"SHOW CHARACTER SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":397,"question":"Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"English","answer_b":"The Structured Query Language","answer_c":"Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages","answer_d":"Swedish","answer_e":"Binary","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":824,"question":"test123","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"test","answer_b":"test2","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Angular"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":995,"question":"Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"x","answer_b":"-","answer_c":"=","answer_d":"*","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":503,"question":"Which tag allows you to add a row in a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<td> and <\/td>","answer_b":"<tr> and <\/tr>","answer_c":"<th> and <\/th>","answer_d":"<cr> and <\/cr>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":580,"question":"What is Joomla in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Set of library enriched with fucntions","answer_b":"Framework for designing dynamic pages","answer_c":"An open source CMS","answer_d":"framework and distribution system for reusable PHP components","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":180,"question":"Docker can build images automatically by reading the instructions from:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker.config","answer_b":"docker.json","answer_c":"docker.yaml","answer_d":"Dockerfile","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":909,"question":"_________ service is automatically created for you K8s cluster creation and takes care of the internal routing of the cluster.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"NodePort","answer_b":"Load Balancer","answer_c":"Headless","answer_d":"ClusterIP","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":859,"question":"How to copy a file from a docker container to the local system.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ sudo docker cp","answer_b":"$ sudo docker cut","answer_c":"$ sudo docker copy","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":707,"question":"Which is the environment variable which holds your home directory information?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HOME.","answer_b":"ROOT.","answer_c":"ADMINISTRATOR","answer_d":"It's generated dynamically","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":618,"question":"How can we check if the value of a given variable is a number?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"numeric(true)","answer_b":"numeric()","answer_c":"is_numeric()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":864,"question":"How to create a volume which docker container will use to store data.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker --volume create","answer_b":"$ docker volume create","answer_c":"$ docker create volume","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":957,"question":"At its core, Kubernetes is a platform for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Provisioning machines (similar to Puppet, Ansible)","answer_b":"Running and scheduling container applications on a cluster","answer_c":"Packaging software in containers","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1056,"question":"Which of the following values would give you the hostname of the remote host in your Ansible Playbook?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\"{{ ansible_hostname }}\"","answer_b":"\"{{ hostname }}\"","answer_c":"\"{{ server_hostname }}\"","answer_d":"\"{{ host }}\"","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":306,"question":"How to convert a category into a tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to install Categories and Tags Converter from the Export option under Tools section.","answer_b":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to install Categories and Tags Converter from the Import option under Tools section.","answer_c":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to Uninstall Categories and Tags Converter from the  Import option under Tools section.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":947,"question":"Write a command to create deployment?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl --create f Deployment.yaml \u2013record","answer_b":"kubectl create f Deployment.yaml \u2013record","answer_c":"kubectl create \u2013f Deployment.yaml \u2013record","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":853,"question":"How to stop a docker container immediately?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker terminate","answer_b":"$ docker kill","answer_c":"$ docker stop","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":686,"question":"Which command can be used to write onto other currently logged in user\u2019s console output terminal.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"notify","answer_b":"alert","answer_c":"write","answer_d":"broadcast","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":682,"question":"Expand JFS in context of file system?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Journal File System","answer_b":"Journal Failing System","answer_c":"Journal File Service","answer_d":"Journal Failing Service","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":221,"question":"The command to remove rows from a table \"MOVIE\" is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REMOVE FROM MOVIE","answer_b":"DROP FROM MOVIE","answer_c":"DELETE FROM MOVIE WHERE","answer_d":"UPDATE FROM MOVIE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":125,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<heading>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<h6>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":750,"question":"What is Minikube","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specification of a Kubernetes API object in JSON or YAML format","answer_b":"A pod object that a kubelet uses to represent a static pod","answer_c":"A tool for running Kubernetes locally","answer_d":"An abstraction used by Kubernetes to support multiple virtual clusters on the same physical cluster","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":993,"question":"Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"onchange","answer_b":"onmouseclick","answer_c":"onmouseover","answer_d":"onclick","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":51,"question":"Which command can you use to re-execute a previous command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"!cat","answer_b":"!!","answer_c":"!a","answer_d":"!3","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"bash","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":505,"question":"Which of the following is an attribute of the <Table> tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SRC","answer_b":"BOLD","answer_c":"CELLPADDING","answer_d":"LINK","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":34,"question":"Which command is used to create file archives in Linux?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"arc","answer_b":"zip","answer_c":"ps","answer_d":"tar","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":721,"question":"Which command shows merged kubeconfig settings?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl config view","answer_b":"kubectl config list","answer_c":"kubectl config show","answer_d":"kubectl config print","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":894,"question":"__________ runs on each node and ensures containers are running in a pod.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Etcd","answer_b":"Flanneld","answer_c":"Scheduler","answer_d":"Kubectl","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":982,"question":"How to write an IF statement for executing some code if \"i\" is NOT equal to 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"if (i != 5)","answer_b":"if (i <> 5)","answer_c":"if i =! 5 then","answer_d":"if i <> 5","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":151,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<movie>","answer_b":"<media>","answer_c":"<type=\"video\">","answer_d":"<video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":216,"question":"Which is the right syntax for the DISTINCT SQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT DIFFERENT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_b":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 WHERE table;","answer_c":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":933,"question":"What is a load balancer in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"load balancer is a method for seperating service","answer_b":"load balancer is a method for exposing service","answer_c":"load balancer is a method for partitioning service","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":615,"question":"What does the unlink() function do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The unlink() function is dedicated for file system handling. It simply deletes the file given as entry.","answer_b":"The unlink() function is not dedicated for file system handling. It does not deletes the file given as entry.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":656,"question":"Which filter can be applied on lines of text for arranging in ascending or descending order?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"sort","answer_b":"arrange","answer_c":"collate","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":953,"question":"Egress is incorrectly speed Ingress","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"false","answer_b":"true","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1036,"question":"Which command will you use to check your Ansible version?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ansible-ctl --version","answer_b":"ansible --version","answer_c":"ansible v","answer_d":"ansiblectl v","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":845,"question":"How to list all the docker images pulled on the system with image details such as TAG\/IMAGE ID\/SIZE etc.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker img","answer_b":"$ docker --images","answer_c":"$ docker images","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":497,"question":"Which of the following attribute is used to group elements?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"item","answer_b":"itemgroup","answer_c":"itemcheck","answer_d":"itemprop","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":748,"question":"The API server is also known as:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubeapi","answer_b":"kube-server","answer_c":"k8s-apiserver","answer_d":"kube-apiserver","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":148,"question":"Which doctype is correct for HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<!DOCTYPE HTML5>","answer_b":"<!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC>","answer_c":"<!DOCTYPE html>","answer_d":"<HTML5>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1052,"question":"What does 'become: yes' mean in Ansible playbooks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It means that the command must be retried until it succeeds","answer_b":"It means that the service needs to be started once installed","answer_c":"It means that the worker node should become a manager node","answer_d":"It means that we would run all commands as root","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":1044,"question":"Which argument do you need to specify in order to run a specific Ansible module?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"--modules","answer_b":"-m","answer_c":"-ml","answer_d":"--ansible-module","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":915,"question":"What are the responsibilities of a node controller?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To assign a CIDR block to the nodes","answer_b":"To monitor the health of the nodes","answer_c":"To maintain the list of nodes","answer_d":"All of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":750,"question":"What is Minikube","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specification of a Kubernetes API object in JSON or YAML format","answer_b":"A pod object that a kubelet uses to represent a static pod","answer_c":"A tool for running Kubernetes locally","answer_d":"An abstraction used by Kubernetes to support multiple virtual clusters on the same physical cluster","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":707,"question":"Which is the environment variable which holds your home directory information?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HOME.","answer_b":"ROOT.","answer_c":"ADMINISTRATOR","answer_d":"It's generated dynamically","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":994,"question":"How do you declare a JavaScript variable?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"v carName;","answer_b":"variable carName;","answer_c":"var carName;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1043,"question":"What are Ansible ad-hoc commands?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are commands which helps you execute simple tasks without the need of creating playbooks","answer_b":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are also known as Ansible playbooks","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":317,"question":"How many Posts and Pages can you have?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"I can have 100 posts and 100 pages","answer_b":"Depends on the theme I'm using.","answer_c":"There is no limit on the number of posts or pages you can have.","answer_d":"There is no limit on the number of posts but I can have only certain amount of pages.","answer_e":"Depending on your plan, you can have a different amount of pages and posts.","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":933,"question":"What is a load balancer in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"load balancer is a method for seperating service","answer_b":"load balancer is a method for exposing service","answer_c":"load balancer is a method for partitioning service","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":278,"question":"Which of the following is a WordPress function used to execute a database query?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<?php $wpdb->run_query('query'); ?>","answer_b":"<?php $wpdb->fetch('query'); ?>","answer_c":"<?php $wpdb->mysql_query('query'); ?>","answer_d":"<?php $wpdb->query('query'); ?>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":891,"question":"Is it possible to build environment-agnostic systems with Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":12,"question":"Which command is used to create an empty file.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mtfile","answer_b":"mkfile","answer_c":"file","answer_d":"touch","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":705,"question":"Deployment Controllers are part of","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Master Controller Manager","answer_b":"kube-scheduler","answer_c":"etcd manager","answer_d":"API Controller Manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"A Deployment provides declarative updates for Pods and ReplicaSets.You describe a desired state in a Deployment, and the Deployment Controller changes the actual state to the desired state at a controlled rate. You can define Deployments to create new ReplicaSets, or to remove existing Deployments and adopt all their resources with new Deployments.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":914,"question":"The Kubernetes Network proxy runs on which node?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Master Node","answer_b":"Worker Node","answer_c":"All the nodes","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":991,"question":"JavaScript is the same as Java.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"False","answer_b":"True","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":61,"question":"All variables in PHP start with which symbol?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"!","answer_c":"#","answer_d":"$","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":59,"question":"PHP server scripts are surrounded by delimiters, which?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<&>...<\/&>","answer_b":"<?php...?>","answer_c":"<?php>...<\/?>","answer_d":"<script>...<\/script>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":18,"question":"Which is the best tool to use for logging in remotely?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"rsh","answer_b":"ssh","answer_c":"telnet","answer_d":"login","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":10,"question":"Which of the following is a command in Linux?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"w","answer_b":"x","answer_c":"t","answer_d":"All of the Above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":255,"question":"What is a Child Theme?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The child theme is an extension of the sub-child theme","answer_b":"The child theme is an extension of the parent theme","answer_c":"The child theme is an extension of the super parent theme","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1062,"question":"Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Controller?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan make:controller controller_name","answer_b":"php artisan create:controller controller_name","answer_c":"php artisan controller create controller_name","answer_d":"php artisan controller:make controller_name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":615,"question":"What does the unlink() function do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The unlink() function is dedicated for file system handling. It simply deletes the file given as entry.","answer_b":"The unlink() function is not dedicated for file system handling. It does not deletes the file given as entry.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":452,"question":"Which Is not a property of attribute behaviour of <Marquee> Tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Blur","answer_b":"Slide","answer_c":"Alternate","answer_d":"Scroll","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1067,"question":"Which artisan command will you used to enable maintenance mode in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan maintenance","answer_b":"php artisan down","answer_c":"php artisan stop","answer_d":"php artisan pause","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":881,"question":"Which are the default networks in Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The default networks in Docker include bridge, host and none.","answer_b":"The default networks in Docker include rope, pin and halt.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1050,"question":"Which argument will you use to specify a variable for your Ansible playbook?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-v","answer_b":"-e","answer_c":"-c","answer_d":"-a","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1064,"question":"Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Model?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan create:model ModelName","answer_b":"php artisan model:make ModelName","answer_c":"php artisan model create ModelName","answer_d":"php artisan make:model ModelName","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":488,"question":"HTML Uses","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Fixed Tags Defined By The Language","answer_b":"Pre-specified Tags","answer_c":"Tags Only For Linking","answer_d":"User Defined Tags","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":215,"question":"Which command is used to modify column names or table structure?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"MODIFY","answer_b":"ADD","answer_c":"CHANGE","answer_d":"ALTER","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":604,"question":"Will a comparison of an integer 12 and a string \"13\" work in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"In PHP you can compare strings with numbers.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":904,"question":"Kube-apiserver on kubernetes master is designed to scale.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Vertically","answer_b":"Horizontally","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":725,"question":"How to list all Kubernetes pods in the current namespace, with more details?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get pods -o wide","answer_b":"kubectl get pods -f more","answer_c":"kubectl get pods -v","answer_d":"kubectl get pods -o details","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1052,"question":"What does 'become: yes' mean in Ansible playbooks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It means that the command must be retried until it succeeds","answer_b":"It means that the service needs to be started once installed","answer_c":"It means that the worker node should become a manager node","answer_d":"It means that we would run all commands as root","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":106,"question":"What is WordPress in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Set of library enriched with fucntions","answer_b":"An open source CMS (Content Management System)","answer_c":"Framework for designing dynamic pages","answer_d":"framework and distribution system for reusable PHP components","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":702,"question":"Which command can be used to display basic information about your server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"uname","answer_b":"info","answer_c":"ls","answer_d":"show","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":636,"question":"Multiple inheritance is supported in PHP.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":127,"question":"What is the correct HTML for adding a background color?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<body bg=\"yellow\">","answer_b":"<background>yellow<\/background>","answer_c":"<body style=\"background-color:yellow;\">","answer_d":"<body style bg=\"yellow\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":549,"question":"Is PHP case sensitive","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Depending on the PHP version either Yes and No","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":324,"question":"You have lost access to your admin area and can't recover it with email. What do you do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Delete your themes folder.","answer_b":"Reinstall Wordpress.","answer_c":"Install a plugin to recover your password.","answer_d":"Add a new user with admin privileges in MySQL.","answer_e":"Reset the password of your user through MySQL.","answer_f":"Register a new user and set it as an administrator via your panel."},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":351,"question":"What is a composite key?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"its is a key that is defined as the primary key in another table","answer_b":"it is a key that uniquely identifies a record in a database","answer_c":"its is an optional key and allows null values","answer_d":"it is a primary key that consists of more than one field that uniquely identifies a record","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":503,"question":"Which tag allows you to add a row in a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<td> and <\/td>","answer_b":"<tr> and <\/tr>","answer_c":"<th> and <\/th>","answer_d":"<cr> and <\/cr>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":599,"question":"How are objects in PHP passed by?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Objects are passed by value.","answer_b":"Objects are passed by reference.","answer_c":"Neither of the mentioned","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":748,"question":"The API server is also known as:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubeapi","answer_b":"kube-server","answer_c":"k8s-apiserver","answer_d":"kube-apiserver","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":145,"question":"Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":961,"question":"In the context of Kubernetes, what is a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"An application which requires dedicated hardware to run on","answer_b":"A container is a standard unit of software that packages up code and all its dependencies so the application runs quickly and reliably from one computing environment to another","answer_c":"A large metal box that is used to hold or transport something","answer_d":"A unit that stores data on a computer's memory drive","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":321,"question":"You can change your Wordpress themes using?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Wordpress Appearance","answer_b":"Wordpress Settings","answer_c":"Wordpress Plugins","answer_d":"wp-config.php file","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":58,"question":"What does PHP stand for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Personal Hypertext Processor","answer_b":"Private Home Page","answer_c":"PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor","answer_d":"Personal Home Page","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":948,"question":"Which command will you use to list all deployments?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get deploy","answer_b":"kubectl require deployments","answer_c":"kubectl get deployments","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":650,"question":"Which command is used to copy file across different system?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"rcp","answer_b":"scp","answer_c":"mcp","answer_d":"ncp","answer_e":"rsync","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":758,"question":"Which of the following function is used to get length of a string?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"size()","answer_b":"strlen()","answer_c":"length","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"The strlen() function is used to find the length of a string.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":915,"question":"What are the responsibilities of a node controller?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To assign a CIDR block to the nodes","answer_b":"To monitor the health of the nodes","answer_c":"To maintain the list of nodes","answer_d":"All of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":306,"question":"How to convert a category into a tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to install Categories and Tags Converter from the Export option under Tools section.","answer_b":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to install Categories and Tags Converter from the Import option under Tools section.","answer_c":"WordPress provides you an option to change category into tag and tag into a category. For this, you need to Uninstall Categories and Tags Converter from the  Import option under Tools section.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":794,"question":"What is containerization?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"system that is being developed and deployed is bundled and wrapped separately with all its configuration files and dependencies. This bundle is called a container.","answer_b":"an application that is being developed and deployed is bundled and wrapped together with all its configuration files and dependencies. This bundle is called a container.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":606,"question":"How is a constant defined in a PHP script?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"define (\"ACONSTANT\" 123)","answer_b":"define (\"ACONSTANT\", 123);","answer_c":"define (CONSTANT, 123);","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":663,"question":"What is the output of the command \u2018umask \u2013S\u2019?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Shows mask value using symbolic notion.","answer_b":"Shows mask value using octal values.","answer_c":"Removes the current mask value.","answer_d":"Sets new mask value.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":731,"question":"How to compares the current state of the cluster against the state that the cluster would be in if the manifest was applied in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl show -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_b":"kubectl log -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_c":"kubectl state -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_d":"kubectl diff -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1045,"question":"What does the Ansible setup module do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It helps you setup Ansible on the master server","answer_b":"It helps you install Ansible on all of your servers","answer_c":"It shows you the information that the Ansible master server has about a host","answer_d":"It sets up the connection between the master and the worker nodes","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":18,"question":"Which is the best tool to use for logging in remotely?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"rsh","answer_b":"ssh","answer_c":"telnet","answer_d":"login","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":314,"question":"What websites can you build with WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Shop","answer_b":"Blog","answer_c":"Betting website","answer_d":"All of the mentioned","answer_e":"A Learning platform","answer_f":"News website"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":718,"question":"Which command is used to create a Kubernetes service?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl set service","answer_b":"kubectl create service","answer_c":"kubectl deploy service","answer_d":"kubectl expose","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":897,"question":"Replication Controllers and Deployment Controllers are part of","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"API Controller Manager","answer_b":"Etcd manager","answer_c":"Master Controller Manager","answer_d":"Kubeadm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":297,"question":"In which programming language WordPress is written?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Java","answer_b":"Node","answer_c":"PHP","answer_d":"Javascript","answer_e":"VueJS","answer_f":"Python"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1053,"question":"What is the Ansible setup module used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Gathers facts about remote hosts","answer_b":"Setup Ansible on remote hosts","answer_c":"Setup ansible on a master host","answer_d":"Setup your SSH keys","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1044,"question":"Which argument do you need to specify in order to run a specific Ansible module?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"--modules","answer_b":"-m","answer_c":"-ml","answer_d":"--ansible-module","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":668,"question":"What will the following command do - $ chmod 888 file","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It enables r,w,x premissions for all users","answer_b":"It disables r,w,x premissions for all users","answer_c":"It enables r,w,x permissions only for owner of the file","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"We can provide the permission values in octal number system and 888 is not a valid octal number.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":757,"question":"Which of the following is correct about constants?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To define a constant you have to use define() function.","answer_b":"To retrieve the value of a constant, you have to simply specify its name.","answer_c":"Both of the mentioned answers.","answer_d":"None of the mentioned answers.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":375,"question":"Once a table has been created in MySQL, its structure cannot be altered","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":895,"question":"_______ manages the assigning nodes to pods depending on resource availability.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Etcd","answer_b":"Flanneld","answer_c":"Scheduler","answer_d":"Kubectl","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1001,"question":"Which of the following is not a component of a Master Node?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Scheduler","answer_b":"Controller Manager","answer_c":"API server","answer_d":"kubectl","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":721,"question":"Which command shows merged kubeconfig settings?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl config view","answer_b":"kubectl config list","answer_c":"kubectl config show","answer_d":"kubectl config print","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":652,"question":"What is the She-bang line in a shell script","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"#","answer_b":"#!","answer_c":"!#","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":160,"question":"Which HTML element defines navigation links?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<nav>","answer_b":"<navigate>","answer_c":"<navigation>","answer_d":"<navlink>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":980,"question":"How do you call a function named \"myFunction\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"myFunction()","answer_b":"call myFunction()","answer_c":"call function myFunction()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":749,"question":"What is the Container Runtime?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Software that is responsible for running containers","answer_b":"An API object that manages a replicated application","answer_c":"Stored instance of a Container that holds a set of software needed to run an application","answer_d":"A command line tool for communicating with a Kubernetes API server","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":505,"question":"Which of the following is an attribute of the <Table> tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SRC","answer_b":"BOLD","answer_c":"CELLPADDING","answer_d":"LINK","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":714,"question":"What could be used to program additional authentication logic besides available authenticator modules?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kube Vault","answer_b":"Authentication Proxy","answer_c":"Kube Auth Service","answer_d":"Kubernetes Role Manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"Using Authentication Proxy, the API server can extract the information it needs about the user\u2019s identity using the HTTP headers that you specify. Let\u2019s have a quick example to demonstrate this concept:","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":896,"question":"As soon a service starts, ________ daemon running on each node add a set of environment variables on the pod for each active service.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kubectl","answer_b":"Service discovery","answer_c":"Kubeadm","answer_d":"Kubelet","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":667,"question":"Choose the odd one out.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"csh","answer_b":"bsh","answer_c":"ksh","answer_d":"Kernel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"Kernel is the core part of the OS and is odd one the rest are popular shells.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":731,"question":"How to compares the current state of the cluster against the state that the cluster would be in if the manifest was applied in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl show -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_b":"kubectl log -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_c":"kubectl state -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_d":"kubectl diff -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1067,"question":"Which artisan command will you used to enable maintenance mode in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan maintenance","answer_b":"php artisan down","answer_c":"php artisan stop","answer_d":"php artisan pause","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":764,"question":"Which of the following method can be used to create a MySql database using PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mysql_connect()","answer_b":"mysql_query()","answer_c":"mysql_close()","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":"mysql_create()","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"PHP uses mysql_query function to create a MySQL database.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":365,"question":"The ASC and DESC keywords can be used in the same statement","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":623,"question":"How can the result set of Mysql be handled in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The result set can be handled using mysqli_fetch_array, mysqli_fetch_assoc, mysqli_fetch_object or mysqli_fetch_row.","answer_b":"The result set can be handled using mysqli_get_array","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1013,"question":"What Is The Role Of Kube-scheduler?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a port to newly created pods.","answer_b":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a node to old created pods.","answer_c":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a cluster to newly created pods.","answer_d":"kube-scheduler is responsible for discovering the newly created pod and selects an optimal node for them to run on","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1059,"question":"What is HTTP middleware in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTTP middleware is a technique for installing Laravel via HTTP.","answer_b":"HTTP middleware is a technique for filtering HTTP requests.","answer_c":"HTTP middleware is a technique for updating Laravel via HTTP.","answer_d":"HTTP middleware is a web server used by Laravel similar to Apache and Nginx.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1038,"question":"The default Ansible inventory file is located at:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/home\/ansible\/inventory","answer_b":"\/etc\/ansible\/inventory","answer_c":"\/home\/ansible\/hosts","answer_d":"\/etc\/ansible\/hosts","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1067,"question":"Which artisan command will you used to enable maintenance mode in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan maintenance","answer_b":"php artisan down","answer_c":"php artisan stop","answer_d":"php artisan pause","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":625,"question":"Can we export data into an Excel file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":707,"question":"Which is the environment variable which holds your home directory information?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HOME.","answer_b":"ROOT.","answer_c":"ADMINISTRATOR","answer_d":"It's generated dynamically","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":976,"question":"What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called \"xxx.js\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<script name=\"xxx.js\">","answer_b":"<script src=\"xxx.js\">","answer_c":"<script href=\"xxx.js\">","answer_d":"<script declare=\"xxx.js\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":903,"question":"The command to create Kubernetes service is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl expose","answer_b":"kubectl deploy","answer_c":"kubectl run","answer_d":"kubectl set service","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":491,"question":"Which of the following is true about HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTML5 is the next major revision of the HTML standard superseding HTML 4.01, XHTML 1.0, and XHTML 1.1.","answer_b":"HTML5 is a cooperation between the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Web Hypertext Application Technology Working Group (WHATWG).","answer_c":"HTML5 is a standard for structuring and presenting content on the World Wide Web","answer_d":"All of These","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":46,"question":"Which of the following answers refers to a software tool used for searching and installing software packages on Debian and Debian-based Linux distributions?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"rpm","answer_b":"apt-rpm","answer_c":"yum","answer_d":"apt-get","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":946,"question":"Which command will you use to update a Kubernetes deployment?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl setimage deployment\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_b":"kubectl --setimage deployment\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_c":"kubectl setimage deploy\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":709,"question":"Which special namespace is used for special purposes like bootstrapping a cluster?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"default","answer_b":"kube-public","answer_c":"kube-private","answer_d":"kube-default","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kube-public namespace is created automatically and is readable by all users (including those not authenticated). This namespace is mostly reserved for cluster usage, in case that some resources should be visible and readable publicly throughout the whole cluster. The public aspect of this namespace is only a convention, not a requirement.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":503,"question":"Which tag allows you to add a row in a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<td> and <\/td>","answer_b":"<tr> and <\/tr>","answer_c":"<th> and <\/th>","answer_d":"<cr> and <\/cr>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":758,"question":"Which of the following function is used to get length of a string?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"size()","answer_b":"strlen()","answer_c":"length","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"The strlen() function is used to find the length of a string.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":907,"question":"This volume type can be used to share contents within containers in a pod, but will not persist beyond the life of a pod.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"EmptyDir","answer_b":"Local","answer_c":"ConfigMap","answer_d":"FlexVolume","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":178,"question":"Which command is used to build a Docker image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker built username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_b":"docker image -t create username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_c":"docker build -t username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_d":"docker create username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":108,"question":"What is the difference between echo and print?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"They both behave the same","answer_b":"Print can take multiple parameters where as echo cannot","answer_c":"Echo can take multiple parameters where as print cannot","answer_d":"Print is a function where as echo is not.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":619,"question":"How can we access the data sent through the URL with the POST method?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$_POST[\"var\"];","answer_b":"$_REQUEST[\"var\"];","answer_c":"$_GET[\"var\"];","answer_d":"$_PUT[\"var\"];","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":959,"question":"What can you deploy on Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Containers","answer_b":"Virtual machines","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":716,"question":"An abstraction in kubernetes which defines a logical set of pods and a policy to access them.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"node","answer_b":"cluster","answer_c":"service","answer_d":"set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"A service is a grouping of pods that are running on the cluster. Services are \"cheap\" and you can have many services within the cluster.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1006,"question":"Which one is true for Minikube?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Minikube is an all-in-One Kubernetes cluster on our workstation","answer_b":"Minikube multi-node cluster","answer_c":"Minikube is a GUI for Kubernetes","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":357,"question":"Which of the following scripts will run successfully","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Users statistics SELECT customer name FROM customers;","answer_b":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;","answer_c":"SELECT FROM `customers` 'customer name';","answer_d":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers ORDER BY zone WHERE cat_id = 12;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1048,"question":"The -b flag in an Ansible ad-hoc command indicates that the command should be executed with sudo privileges.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"false","answer_b":"true","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":60,"question":"How do you write \"Hello World\" in PHP","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"echo \"Hello World\";","answer_b":"Document.Write(\"Hello World\");","answer_c":"\"Hello World\";","answer_d":"display \"Hello World\";","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":312,"question":"What is the name of the first page you encounter after logging into your web page?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Dashboard","answer_b":"Security question page","answer_c":"WP upgrade option","answer_d":"WPAdmin","answer_e":"Clientarea","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1051,"question":"Ansible playbooks are the basis for a really simple configuration management and multi-machine deployment system, unlike any that already exist, and one that is very well suited to deploying complex applications.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"false","answer_b":"true","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":52,"question":"Which of these commands let you view current jobs being handled by Shell?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"view","answer_b":"jobs","answer_c":"show","answer_d":"execute","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":398,"question":"MySQL runs on which Operating Systems?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Unix And Linux Only","answer_b":"Windows only","answer_c":"Linux And Mac OS-X Only","answer_d":"Unix, Linux, Windows,Mac And Others","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1066,"question":"Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Migration?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan make:migrations create_users_table","answer_b":"php artisan create:migrations create_users_table","answer_c":"php artisan make:migration create_users_table","answer_d":"php artisan make:migrations create_users_table","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":872,"question":"Which is not true about Docker Hub?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Hub is the world's largest library and community for container images","answer_b":"Docker Hub provides an easy way to create, manage, and deliver your teams' container applications","answer_c":"Docker Hub is a totally private repository","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":131,"question":"Which character is used to indicate an end tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/","answer_b":"<","answer_c":"*","answer_d":"^","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":197,"question":"What is the prefix of WordPress tables by default?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"wp_ default","answer_b":"wp_","answer_c":"wp_ in","answer_d":"_wp_","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":961,"question":"In the context of Kubernetes, what is a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"An application which requires dedicated hardware to run on","answer_b":"A container is a standard unit of software that packages up code and all its dependencies so the application runs quickly and reliably from one computing environment to another","answer_c":"A large metal box that is used to hold or transport something","answer_d":"A unit that stores data on a computer's memory drive","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":924,"question":"Which of the following is not a services in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Cluster IP","answer_b":"Node port","answer_c":"Load Balancer","answer_d":"External name","answer_e":"Container Proxy","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":315,"question":"Which color is the official color of the Wordpress.org logo?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Yellow","answer_b":"Purple","answer_c":"Dark grey","answer_d":"White","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":146,"question":"Which HTML element defines the title of a document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<title>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<meta>","answer_d":"<start>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1035,"question":"Which of the following commands will install Ansible on Ubuntu?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"sudo apt install ansible","answer_b":"sudo apt install ansible-controller","answer_c":"sudo apt install ansible-master","answer_d":"sudo apt install ansible-server","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":602,"question":"What is the function func_num_args() used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The function func_num_args() is used to give the string of parameters passed into a function.","answer_b":"The function func_num_args() is used to give the number of parameters passed into a function.","answer_c":"The function func_num_args() is used to give the boolean r of parameters passed into a function.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1060,"question":"Which of the following are true for routes in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"You can not pass any arguments to your routes.","answer_b":"Routes can point to a method on a controller and also dictate which HTTP methods are able to hit that URI.","answer_c":"A route is an endpoint specified by a URI (Uniform Resource Identifier).","answer_d":"Routes can only handle GET requests","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":976,"question":"What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called \"xxx.js\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<script name=\"xxx.js\">","answer_b":"<script src=\"xxx.js\">","answer_c":"<script href=\"xxx.js\">","answer_d":"<script declare=\"xxx.js\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":126,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<break>","answer_b":"<br>","answer_c":"<lb>","answer_d":"<bl>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":749,"question":"What is the Container Runtime?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Software that is responsible for running containers","answer_b":"An API object that manages a replicated application","answer_c":"Stored instance of a Container that holds a set of software needed to run an application","answer_d":"A command line tool for communicating with a Kubernetes API server","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":718,"question":"Which command is used to create a Kubernetes service?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl set service","answer_b":"kubectl create service","answer_c":"kubectl deploy service","answer_d":"kubectl expose","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1052,"question":"What does 'become: yes' mean in Ansible playbooks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It means that the command must be retried until it succeeds","answer_b":"It means that the service needs to be started once installed","answer_c":"It means that the worker node should become a manager node","answer_d":"It means that we would run all commands as root","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":889,"question":"If you exit a container accidentally, will you lose all the work?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":7,"question":"How do we change permissions on files","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"chown","answer_b":"chmod","answer_c":"chattr","answer_d":"lsattr","answer_e":"We Can't change them","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":59,"question":"PHP server scripts are surrounded by delimiters, which?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<&>...<\/&>","answer_b":"<?php...?>","answer_c":"<?php>...<\/?>","answer_d":"<script>...<\/script>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":217,"question":"What is the use of SQL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Storing data in database","answer_b":"Manipulating data in database","answer_c":"Retrieving data in database","answer_d":"Displaying images","answer_e":"Managing queries","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":547,"question":"What does the date_sunset() function returns","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Returns the date of sunset for a given day \/ location","answer_b":"Returns the time of sunset for a given day \/ location","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1000,"question":"Kubernetes can be configured in a multi-Master Node configuration. True or False?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":604,"question":"Will a comparison of an integer 12 and a string \"13\" work in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"In PHP you can compare strings with numbers.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":616,"question":"How do we check if a given variable is empty?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"With the null() function.","answer_b":"With the empty() function.","answer_c":"With the isitnull() function.","answer_d":"With the isitempty() function.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":983,"question":"How does a WHILE loop start?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"while (i <= 10)","answer_b":"while i = 1 to 10","answer_c":"while (i <= 10; i++)","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":614,"question":"What does the unset() function do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The unset() function is dedicated for variable management. It will make a variable undefined.","answer_b":"The unset() function is not dedicated for variable management. It will make a variable defined.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":865,"question":"How to install a docker plugin vieux\/sshfs with debug environment set to 1.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker plugin install vieux\/sshfs DEBUG=1","answer_b":"$ docker install vieux\/sshfs DEBUG=1","answer_c":"$ docker install plugins vieux\/sshfs DEBUG=1","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":51,"question":"Which command can you use to re-execute a previous command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"!cat","answer_b":"!!","answer_c":"!a","answer_d":"!3","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"bash","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":807,"question":"How to kill a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker terminated <container_id>","answer_b":"docker kill <container_id>","answer_c":"$ docker --kill <container_id>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":855,"question":"How to login into docker hub.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker $login","answer_b":"$ docker --log","answer_c":"$ docker login","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":61,"question":"All variables in PHP start with which symbol?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"!","answer_c":"#","answer_d":"$","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":897,"question":"Replication Controllers and Deployment Controllers are part of","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"API Controller Manager","answer_b":"Etcd manager","answer_c":"Master Controller Manager","answer_d":"Kubeadm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":101,"question":"Can you run several versions of PHP at the same time?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":662,"question":"Which command can give first found difference between two file after comparing?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"diff","answer_b":"cmp","answer_c":"Common","answer_d":"stat","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":718,"question":"Which command is used to create a Kubernetes service?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl set service","answer_b":"kubectl create service","answer_c":"kubectl deploy service","answer_d":"kubectl expose","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":272,"question":"What is the difference between installing and activating a theme?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"When a theme is activated it\u2019s what\u2019s controlling your site, while an uninstalled theme is simply part of your theme library and available to activate.","answer_b":"When a theme is deactivated it\u2019s what\u2019s controlling your site, while an installed theme is simply part of your theme library and available to activate.","answer_c":"When a theme is activated it\u2019s what\u2019s controlling your site, while an installed theme is simply part of your theme library and available to activate.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":379,"question":"What will be the output of the query SELECT * FROM `members` LIMIT 1, 2;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will generate an error","answer_b":"the query will return all records from the members table","answer_c":"the query will return the first 2 records","answer_d":"the query will return skip the first record then return the following 2 records only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":997,"question":"Is JavaScript case-sensitive?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":913,"question":"Which of the following are core Kubernetes objects?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Pods, Services, Volumes","answer_b":"Pods, Docker, Volumes","answer_c":"Pods, Services, Droplets","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":16,"question":"Which command is used to create new directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"dir","answer_b":"newdir","answer_c":"mkdir","answer_d":"cdir","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":321,"question":"You can change your Wordpress themes using?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Wordpress Appearance","answer_b":"Wordpress Settings","answer_c":"Wordpress Plugins","answer_d":"wp-config.php file","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":604,"question":"Will a comparison of an integer 12 and a string \"13\" work in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"In PHP you can compare strings with numbers.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":214,"question":"What does the WHERE SQL operator does:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"restricts the set of rows to the selection of those records for which the condition is true","answer_b":"converts the value of a column or function to a different type","answer_c":"changes the order of output rows","answer_d":"eliminates all row repeats from the result set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1062,"question":"Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Controller?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan make:controller controller_name","answer_b":"php artisan create:controller controller_name","answer_c":"php artisan controller create controller_name","answer_d":"php artisan controller:make controller_name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":361,"question":"What will be the output of the following query INSERT INTO students (student name) VALUE ('James Lenon');","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"a student record with the name James Lenon will be added into the students table","answer_b":"the above query will generate an error message.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":852,"question":"How to stop a container with container id mentioned in the command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker ter 109cb6nw","answer_b":"$ docker stop -ls 109cb6nw","answer_c":"$ docker stop 109cb6nw","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":149,"question":"Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<footer>","answer_b":"<section>","answer_c":"<bottom>","answer_d":"<down>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1023,"question":"What does the FROM instruction do in a Dockerfile?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"FROM creates a layer from a base Docker image.","answer_b":"FROM specifies the creator of the image","answer_c":"FROM is an invalid instruction","answer_d":"FROM adds files from your Docker client\u2019s current directory","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":173,"question":"Where can you  find and share Docker container images?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Swarm","answer_b":"Docker Cloud","answer_c":"Docker Hub","answer_d":"Docker Git","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":365,"question":"The ASC and DESC keywords can be used in the same statement","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1059,"question":"What is HTTP middleware in Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTTP middleware is a technique for installing Laravel via HTTP.","answer_b":"HTTP middleware is a technique for filtering HTTP requests.","answer_c":"HTTP middleware is a technique for updating Laravel via HTTP.","answer_d":"HTTP middleware is a web server used by Laravel similar to Apache and Nginx.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":116,"question":"Which of the following is used to declare a constant","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"const","answer_b":"define","answer_c":"constant","answer_d":"def","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":875,"question":"If the Plesk server can't run Docker locally, you can still connect to a remote Docker server to manage containers. You'll need:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A virtuozzo 6 container","answer_b":"One separate ready-to-code environment","answer_c":"A Windows Server","answer_d":"The Plesk Docker extension","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":392,"question":"Which among the following have the maximum available bytes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Varchar","answer_b":"Text Type","answer_c":"Both Varchar And Char","answer_d":"Char","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":530,"question":"Which of the following is not a style tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<b>","answer_b":"All are style tags","answer_c":"<i>","answer_d":"<tt>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":946,"question":"Which command will you use to update a Kubernetes deployment?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl setimage deployment\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_b":"kubectl --setimage deployment\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_c":"kubectl setimage deploy\/Deployment tomcat = tomcat:6.0","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":686,"question":"Which command can be used to write onto other currently logged in user\u2019s console output terminal.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"notify","answer_b":"alert","answer_c":"write","answer_d":"broadcast","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":615,"question":"What does the unlink() function do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The unlink() function is dedicated for file system handling. It simply deletes the file given as entry.","answer_b":"The unlink() function is not dedicated for file system handling. It does not deletes the file given as entry.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":606,"question":"How is a constant defined in a PHP script?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"define (\"ACONSTANT\" 123)","answer_b":"define (\"ACONSTANT\", 123);","answer_c":"define (CONSTANT, 123);","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":488,"question":"HTML Uses","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Fixed Tags Defined By The Language","answer_b":"Pre-specified Tags","answer_c":"Tags Only For Linking","answer_d":"User Defined Tags","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1054,"question":"Which command would you use to gather facts with Ansible?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ansible your_server -m gather","answer_b":"ansible your_server -m setup","answer_c":"ansible your_server -m info","answer_d":"ansible your_server -m fact","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":680,"question":"How can you display the top 10 number of lines of a file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"head \u2212n 10 file.txt","answer_b":"head -f 10 file.txt","answer_c":"head --display-only 10 file.txt","answer_d":"head -show 10 file.txt","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":300,"question":"What is the difference between character 23 and x23?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"23 specifies the octal 23 and x23 determine the hex 23.","answer_b":"23 specifies the hex 23 and x23 determine the octal 23","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":779,"question":"What is the difference between Numeric and Associative","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The Numeric arrays can store numbers, strings and any object but their index will be represented by numbers while the Associative arrays have their index stored as string.","answer_b":"There are no Associative arrays","answer_c":"The Numeric and Associative arrays differ only in the maximum allowed objects in them.","answer_d":"The Numeric arrays can store numbers, strings and any object but their index will be represented by numbers while the Associative arrays each element in the main array can also be an array.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":371,"question":"Null is used as a place holder for optional fields","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":106,"question":"What is WordPress in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Set of library enriched with fucntions","answer_b":"An open source CMS (Content Management System)","answer_c":"Framework for designing dynamic pages","answer_d":"framework and distribution system for reusable PHP components","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":209,"question":"UPDATE keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"to create database elements","answer_b":"to change data","answer_c":"to manage users","answer_d":"to select data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":216,"question":"Which is the right syntax for the DISTINCT SQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT DIFFERENT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_b":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 WHERE table;","answer_c":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":996,"question":"What will the following code return: Boolean(10 > 9)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"true","answer_b":"NaN","answer_c":"false","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1052,"question":"What does 'become: yes' mean in Ansible playbooks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It means that the command must be retried until it succeeds","answer_b":"It means that the service needs to be started once installed","answer_c":"It means that the worker node should become a manager node","answer_d":"It means that we would run all commands as root","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":883,"question":"What is the difference between Docker image and layer.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker image is created with a series of read-only layers and layer in docker represents instructions on the Dockerfile of the image.","answer_b":"Docker image is created with a series of write-only layers and layer in docker represents instructions on the Dockerfile of the container.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":957,"question":"At its core, Kubernetes is a platform for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Provisioning machines (similar to Puppet, Ansible)","answer_b":"Running and scheduling container applications on a cluster","answer_c":"Packaging software in containers","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":692,"question":"Which service runs on each Kubernetes node and ensures containers are running in a pod?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"etcd","answer_b":"kubelet","answer_c":"scheduler","answer_d":"kubeadm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kubelet is the primary \u201cnode agent\u201d that runs on each node. It can register the node with the apiserver using one of: the hostname; a flag to override the hostname; or specific logic for a cloud provider.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":960,"question":"What is a cluster?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A system made up of multiple servers and other resources","answer_b":"A computer program or device that provides services to other computers","answer_c":"A specific set of ordered operations","answer_d":"A software package that performs a specific function for an end user","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":723,"question":"Which command is used to create resources in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl create -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_b":"kubectl deploy -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_c":"kubectl apply -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_d":"kubectl fuse -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":720,"question":"Cronjobs in kubernetes run in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UTC only","answer_b":"Based on NTP settings","answer_c":"Master node local timezone","answer_d":"GMT only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":255,"question":"What is a Child Theme?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The child theme is an extension of the sub-child theme","answer_b":"The child theme is an extension of the parent theme","answer_c":"The child theme is an extension of the super parent theme","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":838,"question":"Docker host's IP address by default is 192.168.99.100","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1080,"question":"Which command do we need to use if we want to see all packages installed on the system (Ubuntu)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"dpkg -l","answer_b":"packageall -l","answer_c":"dpkg -a","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":81,"question":"The if statement is used to execute some code only if a specified condition is true","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":312,"question":"What is the name of the first page you encounter after logging into your web page?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Dashboard","answer_b":"Security question page","answer_c":"WP upgrade option","answer_d":"WPAdmin","answer_e":"Clientarea","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":108,"question":"What is the difference between echo and print?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"They both behave the same","answer_b":"Print can take multiple parameters where as echo cannot","answer_c":"Echo can take multiple parameters where as print cannot","answer_d":"Print is a function where as echo is not.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1077,"question":"You are logged in as a normal user and you see a file with 444(-r--r--r--) permission. Can you delete it with the `rm` command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"We can't be certain, it depends on the permissions of the parent folder","answer_b":"Yes, can delete it without a problem","answer_c":"No, we don't have the proper permissions","answer_d":"We can delete it only from the GUI but not from CLI.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":899,"question":"Kubernetes uses _____________ to connect to ouath 2 providers to offload the authentication to external services.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Webhook Token Authentication","answer_b":"Keystone Password","answer_c":"OpenID Connect Tokens","answer_d":"Authentication Proxy","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":806,"question":"How to stop a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker trim <container_id>","answer_b":"$ docker dead <container_id>","answer_c":"$ docker stop <container_id>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":775,"question":"Using which of the following way can you embed PHP code in an HTML page?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<?php PHP code goes here ?>","answer_b":"<?php PHP code goes here php?>","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":882,"question":"How can you monitor Docker in production?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"You can use Docker tools such as Docker pin and docker file for monitoring","answer_b":"You can use Docker tools such as Docker logs and docker plugins for monitoring","answer_c":"You can use Docker tools such as Docker events and docker stats for monitoring","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":908,"question":"__________________ is responsible for health check of the pods running on individual nodes","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kubectl","answer_b":"Kubelet","answer_c":"Kube scheduler","answer_d":"Kube controller manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":702,"question":"Which command can be used to display basic information about your server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"uname","answer_b":"info","answer_c":"ls","answer_d":"show","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":310,"question":"What dos the acronym CMS stands for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Common manager system","answer_b":"Content manager system","answer_c":"Content management system","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":724,"question":"How to list all Kubernetes services in the current namespace?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get-all services","answer_b":"kubectl print services","answer_c":"kubectl dump services","answer_d":"kubectl get services","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":795,"question":"What are Docker Images?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker image is the source of Docker virtualization.","answer_b":"Docker image is the source of Docker system.","answer_c":"Docker image is the source of Docker container.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":197,"question":"What is the prefix of WordPress tables by default?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"wp_ default","answer_b":"wp_","answer_c":"wp_ in","answer_d":"_wp_","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":49,"question":"Which of the following key combinations allows to terminate the current process in Linux shell?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ctrl + C","answer_b":"Ctrl + Z","answer_c":"Ctrl + A","answer_d":"Ctrl + L","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":891,"question":"Is it possible to build environment-agnostic systems with Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1056,"question":"Which of the following values would give you the hostname of the remote host in your Ansible Playbook?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\"{{ ansible_hostname }}\"","answer_b":"\"{{ hostname }}\"","answer_c":"\"{{ server_hostname }}\"","answer_d":"\"{{ host }}\"","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":135,"question":"How can you make a numbered list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<ol>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<list>","answer_d":"<ul>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":537,"question":"Which tag creates a check box for a form in HTML?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<checkbox>","answer_b":"<input checkbox>","answer_c":"<input=checkbox>","answer_d":"<input type=\"checkbox\">","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":681,"question":"Who designed the Linux OS?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Linus Torvalds","answer_b":"Steve Jobs","answer_c":"Steve Wozniak","answer_d":"Steve Linus","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":644,"question":"How can you set the default rwx permission to all users on every file which is created in the current shell?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"umask  0777","answer_b":"chmod  777","answer_c":"chown  777","answer_d":"umask  0666","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"bash","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":8,"question":"When do we use the GREP command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"When we want to search for a string","answer_b":"To find a file","answer_c":"To find a directory","answer_d":"To show all directories which have the string in their name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":173,"question":"Where can you  find and share Docker container images?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Swarm","answer_b":"Docker Cloud","answer_c":"Docker Hub","answer_d":"Docker Git","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":806,"question":"How to stop a container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker trim <container_id>","answer_b":"$ docker dead <container_id>","answer_c":"$ docker stop <container_id>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1043,"question":"What are Ansible ad-hoc commands?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are commands which helps you execute simple tasks without the need of creating playbooks","answer_b":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are also known as Ansible playbooks","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1050,"question":"Which argument will you use to specify a variable for your Ansible playbook?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-v","answer_b":"-e","answer_c":"-c","answer_d":"-a","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":303,"question":"What is moderate comment in WordPress.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Comments by admin on a post are not published directly unless the visitors provides it. It is called moderation.","answer_b":"Comments by admin on a post are not published directly unless the clients provides it. It is called moderation.","answer_c":"Comments by visitors on a post are not published directly unless the admin provides it. It is called moderation.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":903,"question":"The command to create Kubernetes service is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl expose","answer_b":"kubectl deploy","answer_c":"kubectl run","answer_d":"kubectl set service","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":958,"question":"In Kubernetes, a node is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A tool for starting a kubernetes cluster on a local machine","answer_b":"A worker machine","answer_c":"A machine that coordinates the scheduling and management of application containers on the cluster","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":153,"question":"The HTML global attribute, \"contenteditable\" is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Specify whether the content of an element should be editable or not","answer_b":"Update content from the server","answer_c":"Specifies a context menu for an element. The menu appears when a user right-clicks on the element","answer_d":"Return the position of the first found occurrence of content inside a string","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":764,"question":"Which of the following method can be used to create a MySql database using PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mysql_connect()","answer_b":"mysql_query()","answer_c":"mysql_close()","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":"mysql_create()","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"PHP uses mysql_query function to create a MySQL database.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1038,"question":"The default Ansible inventory file is located at:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/home\/ansible\/inventory","answer_b":"\/etc\/ansible\/inventory","answer_c":"\/home\/ansible\/hosts","answer_d":"\/etc\/ansible\/hosts","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":128,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element to define important text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<b>","answer_b":"<i>","answer_c":"<important>","answer_d":"<strong>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":879,"question":"What is the reason for using Volumes in Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To create exceptions to the `--read-only` mode.","answer_b":"To add plugins for extended file attributes.","answer_c":"To fail access to persisted data such as data in a database.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":681,"question":"Who designed the Linux OS?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Linus Torvalds","answer_b":"Steve Jobs","answer_c":"Steve Wozniak","answer_d":"Steve Linus","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":986,"question":"How to insert a comment that has more than one line?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/*This comment has more than one line*\/","answer_b":"<!--This comment has more than one line-->","answer_c":"\/\/This comment has more than one line\/\/","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":663,"question":"What is the output of the command \u2018umask \u2013S\u2019?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Shows mask value using symbolic notion.","answer_b":"Shows mask value using octal values.","answer_c":"Removes the current mask value.","answer_d":"Sets new mask value.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":315,"question":"Which color is the official color of the Wordpress.org logo?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Yellow","answer_b":"Purple","answer_c":"Dark grey","answer_d":"White","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":532,"question":"There are ____ different heading tags in HTML","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"4","answer_b":"7","answer_c":"6","answer_d":"5","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":749,"question":"What is the Container Runtime?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Software that is responsible for running containers","answer_b":"An API object that manages a replicated application","answer_c":"Stored instance of a Container that holds a set of software needed to run an application","answer_d":"A command line tool for communicating with a Kubernetes API server","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":123,"question":"What does HTML stand for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Hyper Text Markup Language","answer_b":"Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language","answer_c":"Home Tool Markup Language","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":371,"question":"Null is used as a place holder for optional fields","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":63,"question":"The PHP syntax is most similar to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"JavaScript","answer_b":"Perl and C","answer_c":"VBScript","answer_d":"Bash","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":60,"question":"How do you write \"Hello World\" in PHP","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"echo \"Hello World\";","answer_b":"Document.Write(\"Hello World\");","answer_c":"\"Hello World\";","answer_d":"display \"Hello World\";","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":21,"question":"Which of the following is a text editor that can be used in command mode to edit files on a Linux system?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"vi or vim","answer_b":"lsof","answer_c":"open","answer_d":"edit","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1053,"question":"What is the Ansible setup module used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Gathers facts about remote hosts","answer_b":"Setup Ansible on remote hosts","answer_c":"Setup ansible on a master host","answer_d":"Setup your SSH keys","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":690,"question":"How can we list out all currently executing background processes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ps -e","answer_b":"top","answer_c":"ps faux","answer_d":"proccess -aux","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":533,"question":"In HTML document the tags","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Should be written in upper case","answer_b":"can be written in both uppercase or lowercase","answer_c":"should be written in propercase","answer_d":"should be written in lower case","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":74,"question":"What is a correct way to add a comment in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"*\\...\\*","answer_b":"\/*...*\/","answer_c":"<!--...-->","answer_d":"<comment>...<\/comment>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":878,"question":"How can you make sure your Docker containers and their data are safely backed up?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Backup the \/var\/lib\/docker\/ directory manually  Nothing.","answer_b":"Data stored in Docker containers is backed up to Docker Hub.","answer_c":"Schedule regular Plesk backups. Docker containers are included in Plesk backups.","answer_d":"Set up volume mapping on all containers to store their data in a single location on the server (example, \/data\/) and backup this location.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":439,"question":"Function which causes retrieval of any kind of data from database is considered as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Interface or Signature","answer_b":"Logical signature","answer_c":"Conceptual signature","answer_d":"User friendly signature","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":396,"question":"What kind of replication is supported by the MySQL Server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Multiple-master Replication","answer_b":"MySQL Doesn't Support Replication","answer_c":"Master To Slave Replication","answer_d":"Single File Based Clustering","answer_e":"Master to Master Replication","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":82,"question":"Which operator is used to check if two values are equal and of same data type?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"==","answer_b":"=","answer_c":"===","answer_d":"!=","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1043,"question":"What are Ansible ad-hoc commands?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are commands which helps you execute simple tasks without the need of creating playbooks","answer_b":"Ansible ad-hoc commands are also known as Ansible playbooks","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":816,"question":"Can I use JSON instead of YAML for my compose file in Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":551,"question":"Which of the following is not a Superglobal in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$_SERVER","answer_b":"$_PUT","answer_c":"$_FILES","answer_d":"$_ENV","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":90,"question":"Which of the following keyword terminates the for loop or switch statement and transfers execution to the statement immediately following the for loop or switch?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"break","answer_b":"continue","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":714,"question":"What could be used to program additional authentication logic besides available authenticator modules?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kube Vault","answer_b":"Authentication Proxy","answer_c":"Kube Auth Service","answer_d":"Kubernetes Role Manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"Using Authentication Proxy, the API server can extract the information it needs about the user\u2019s identity using the HTTP headers that you specify. Let\u2019s have a quick example to demonstrate this concept:","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":920,"question":"What are the different components of Kubernetes Architecture?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The Kubernetes Architecture has mainly 2 components \u2013 the master node and the worker node.","answer_b":"The Kubernetes Architecture has mainly 2 components \u2013 the service and the worker path.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":728,"question":"How to list all services sorted by name in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get services --sort-by=.service.name","answer_b":"kubectl get services --sort=.name","answer_c":"kubectl get services --sort-by=.metadata.name","answer_d":"kubectl get services --sort-by=name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":966,"question":"What is the purpose of a ReplicaSet?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To prevent clones from invading other clusters","answer_b":"To monitor and respond to environmental latency","answer_c":"To maintain a stable set of replica Pods running at any given time","answer_d":"To create and maintain volumes","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":575,"question":"What will be printed if we run the following code? <?php $var = 'false';  if ($var) { echo 'true'; } else { echo 'false'; }","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":525,"question":"Which of the following is not a valid alignment attribute?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Left","answer_b":"Top","answer_c":"Right","answer_d":"All of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":420,"question":"What Is a MySQL View?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"VIEWS are virtual tables that do not store any data of their own but display data stored in other tables.","answer_b":"VIEWS are static tables that store data but the data can't be changed","answer_c":"VIEWS are temporary tables that store data which store data only for a certain amount of time","answer_d":"VIEWS are no different that any other tables except they are used for faster loading.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":968,"question":"Which description best fits a DaemonSet?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A way to run a copy of a pod on all or some nodes","answer_b":"A method to manage clusters of pods","answer_c":"A channel through which to pass information between two or more nodes","answer_d":"A system to connect nodes and pods","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":813,"question":"How to build a Dockerfile?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker build <path to docker file>","answer_b":"$ docker build to <path to docker file>","answer_c":"$ docker build in <path to docker file>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":822,"question":"Suppose you have an application that has many dependant services. Will docker compose wait for the current container to be ready to move to the running of the next service?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":215,"question":"Which command is used to modify column names or table structure?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"MODIFY","answer_b":"ADD","answer_c":"CHANGE","answer_d":"ALTER","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":277,"question":"In WordPress, objects are passed by value or by reference.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"In WordPress, all objects are passed by value.","answer_b":"In WordPress, all objects are passed by reference.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":576,"question":"How can we add comments in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/\/ commented code to end of line","answer_b":"\/* commented code here *\/","answer_c":"# commented code to end of line","answer_d":"all of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":158,"question":"Which input type defines a slider control?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"slider","answer_b":"search","answer_c":"range","answer_d":"controls","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":95,"question":"Which of the following gives a string containing PHP script file name in which it is called?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$php_errormsg","answer_b":"$_COOKIE","answer_c":"$_PHP_SELF","answer_d":"$_SESSION","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":909,"question":"_________ service is automatically created for you K8s cluster creation and takes care of the internal routing of the cluster.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"NodePort","answer_b":"Load Balancer","answer_c":"Headless","answer_d":"ClusterIP","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":512,"question":"Text within <EM> \u2026 <\/EM> tag is displayed as ________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"bold","answer_b":"indented","answer_c":"list","answer_d":"italic","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":768,"question":"Which of the following is used to check that a cookie is set or not?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"getcookie() function","answer_b":"$_COOKIE variable","answer_c":"isset() function","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"You can use isset() function to check if a cookie is set or not.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":600,"question":"What does accessing a class via :: means?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":":: is used to access static methods that do not require object initialization.","answer_b":":: is used to access static methods that require object initialization.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1079,"question":"Which command do we need to execute to check the available repos in yum (CentOS)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"yum repolist","answer_b":"yum listrepo","answer_c":"yum searchrepo","answer_d":"yum reposearch","answer_e":"yum reposhow","answer_f":"yum showrepo"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":578,"question":"How do we access the value of 'd' later? $a = array(     'a',     3 => 'b',     1 => 'c',     'd' );","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$a[0]","answer_b":"$a[3]","answer_c":"$a[2]","answer_d":"$a[1]","answer_e":"$a[4]","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":692,"question":"Which service runs on each Kubernetes node and ensures containers are running in a pod?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"etcd","answer_b":"kubelet","answer_c":"scheduler","answer_d":"kubeadm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kubelet is the primary \u201cnode agent\u201d that runs on each node. It can register the node with the apiserver using one of: the hostname; a flag to override the hostname; or specific logic for a cloud provider.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":145,"question":"Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":603,"question":"How is the ternary conditional operator used in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Expression_1?Expression_2 : Expression_3;","answer_b":"Expression_1:Expression_2 : Expression_3;","answer_c":"Expression_1?Expression_2 ? Expression_3;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":709,"question":"Which special namespace is used for special purposes like bootstrapping a cluster?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"default","answer_b":"kube-public","answer_c":"kube-private","answer_d":"kube-default","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kube-public namespace is created automatically and is readable by all users (including those not authenticated). This namespace is mostly reserved for cluster usage, in case that some resources should be visible and readable publicly throughout the whole cluster. The public aspect of this namespace is only a convention, not a requirement.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":313,"question":"How can you get involved with WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Attend Word Camp","answer_b":"Edit the Codex (documentation)","answer_c":"Help in the Forums","answer_d":"All of these","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":375,"question":"Once a table has been created in MySQL, its structure cannot be altered","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":257,"question":"Which CMS powers around 35% of all websites on the internet?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress","answer_b":"Dropal","answer_c":"Joomla","answer_d":"Laravel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":583,"question":"What is the purpose of $_SESSION[]?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Used to register a global variable","answer_b":"none of the above","answer_c":"Used to store variables of the current session","answer_d":"Used to initialize a session.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":834,"question":"Which of the following is a hosted service that provides a Registry with build and testing facilities for Dockerized application images, tools to help you set up and manage your host infrastructure.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Cloud","answer_b":"Docker Compose","answer_c":"Docker Hub","answer_d":"Docker Universal Control Plane","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":838,"question":"Docker host's IP address by default is 192.168.99.100","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},
  {"id":325,"question":"What will happen if two tables have names 'users' and 'USERS'?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"This is not possible because table names are case insensitive","answer_b":"This depends on lower_case_table_names system variable","answer_c":"This is possible only on UNIX\/LINUX","answer_d":"This is possible only on Windows","answer_e":"This is possible because table names are case sensitive","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":378,"question":"What will be the effect of the query SELECT TOP (100) FROM customers when executed against MySQL database.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The query will return 100 records from the database table sorted in descending order","answer_b":"The query will return all records from the database table","answer_c":"The query will generate an error","answer_d":"The query will return 100 records from the database table sorted in ascending order","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":439,"question":"Function which causes retrieval of any kind of data from database is considered as","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Interface or Signature","answer_b":"Logical signature","answer_c":"Conceptual signature","answer_d":"User friendly signature","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":345,"question":"Which type of database management system represents relations using tables?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Network DBMS","answer_b":"Hierachical DBMS","answer_c":"Relational DBMS","answer_d":"Object Oriented DBMS","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":222,"question":"The wildcard in a WHERE clause is useful when?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"An exact match is necessary in a SELECT statement.","answer_b":"An exact match is not possible in a SELECT statement.","answer_c":"An exact match is necessary in a CREATE statement.","answer_d":"An exact match is not possible in a CREATE statement.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":424,"question":"DCL is used for _______?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Managing the changes made by DML statements","answer_b":"Inserting, Deleting and Updating data","answer_c":"Control access to data stored in a database","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":413,"question":"How much character are allowed to create a  database name?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"64","answer_b":"70","answer_c":"75","answer_d":"40","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":420,"question":"What Is a MySQL View?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"VIEWS are virtual tables that do not store any data of their own but display data stored in other tables.","answer_b":"VIEWS are static tables that store data but the data can't be changed","answer_c":"VIEWS are temporary tables that store data which store data only for a certain amount of time","answer_d":"VIEWS are no different that any other tables except they are used for faster loading.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":337,"question":"Which of the following is not a MySQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ENUMERATE","answer_b":"EXPLAIN","answer_c":"KILL","answer_d":"LOAD DATA","answer_e":"SET","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":210,"question":"DML is included into SQL language of:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"managing users","answer_b":"managing transactions","answer_c":"description data","answer_d":"managing data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":348,"question":"The logic model of a database is?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"concerned with the planning of the entire database development life cycle","answer_b":"concerned with the physical implementation of the database","answer_c":"concerned with developing the database model taking into consideration the physical implementation","answer_d":"concerned with developing the database model without taking into consideration the physical implementation or the DBMS","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":357,"question":"Which of the following scripts will run successfully","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Users statistics SELECT customer name FROM customers;","answer_b":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;","answer_c":"SELECT FROM `customers` 'customer name';","answer_d":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers ORDER BY zone WHERE cat_id = 12;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":392,"question":"Which among the following have the maximum available bytes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Varchar","answer_b":"Text Type","answer_c":"Both Varchar And Char","answer_d":"Char","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":393,"question":"The \"father\" Of MySQL Is ______.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Bill Joy","answer_b":"Stephanie Wall","answer_c":"Bill Gates","answer_d":"Michael Widenius","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":207,"question":"DISTINCT keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"There is no such keyword","answer_b":"For selecting only unique records by a specific field","answer_c":"To reduce the load on the server with loss of query performance","answer_d":"To speed up the selection for a specific field","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":234,"question":"Can you insert multiple rows with only one INSERT query?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"It's possible but only with newer MySQL versions","answer_d":"Yes but these inserts cause data corruption","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":339,"question":"Which of the following are not Numeric column types?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BIGINT","answer_b":"LARGEINT","answer_c":"SMALLINT","answer_d":"DOUBLE","answer_e":"DECIMAL","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":474,"question":"What type of join is needed when you wish to return rows that have matching values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Equi-join","answer_b":"All of the mentioned.","answer_c":"Outer join","answer_d":"Natural join","answer_e":"None of the mentioned.","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":391,"question":"Which one is the correct declaration for choosing the 'Character Set' other than default?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Varchar(20);","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"Varchar(20) Character Set;","answer_d":"Varchar(20) Character Set Utf8;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":376,"question":"The syntax for adding a new column to an existing table is ALTER TABLE `table_name` ADD COLUMN `column_name` `data_type`;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},
  {"id":385,"question":"To use 'mysqldbcopy' which privileges are required on the source server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CREATE","answer_b":"UPDATE","answer_c":"SELECT","answer_d":"INSERT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":206,"question":"SQL (Structured Query Language) is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"imperative programming language","answer_b":"the language of structured queries","answer_c":"the language of queries by pattern","answer_d":"DBMS (DataBase Management System)","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":350,"question":"Normalizations is...","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"concerned with the physical implementation of the database","answer_b":"a database design technique that encourages storing data in multiple databases","answer_c":"a database design technique that eliminates relationships from a database","answer_d":"a database design technique used to minimize data redundancy and duplication","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":232,"question":"Which of the following statements are true about SQL injection attacks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Wrapping all variables containing user input by a call to mysql_real_escape_string() makes the code immune to SQL injections.","answer_b":"Parametrized queries do not make code less vulnearable to SQL injections.","answer_c":"SQL injections are not possible, if only emulated prepared statements are used.","answer_d":"Usage of later versions of MySQL, validation, and explicit setting of the charset of user input are valid measures to decrease vulnerability to SQL injections.","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":474,"question":"What type of join is needed when you wish to return rows that have matching values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Equi-join","answer_b":"All of the mentioned.","answer_c":"Outer join","answer_d":"Natural join","answer_e":"None of the mentioned.","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":338,"question":"What is the maximum size of a row in a MyISAM table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"No limit","answer_b":"OS specific","answer_c":"65534","answer_d":"128","answer_e":"2\u2019147\u2019483\u2019648","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":345,"question":"Which type of database management system represents relations using tables?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Network DBMS","answer_b":"Hierachical DBMS","answer_c":"Relational DBMS","answer_d":"Object Oriented DBMS","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":225,"question":"Which command is used to insert a new records in the table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ADD","answer_b":"INSERT INTO","answer_c":"INSERT","answer_d":"NEW","answer_e":"CREATE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":251,"question":"Which of the following will reset the MySQL password for a particular user?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=\u2019password\u2019 WHERE User=\u2019username\u2019;","answer_b":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=PASSWORD(\u2018password\u2019) WHERE User=\u2019username\u2019;","answer_c":"UPDATE mysql.user SET Password=RESET(\u2018password\u2019) WHERE User=\u2019username\u2019;","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":363,"question":"What improvements can be made to the query UPDATE students SET `contact number` = 0999;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The query does not need any improvements","answer_b":"enclose the contact number in single quotes","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":438,"question":"The data type BLOB stands for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Binary Large Object","answer_b":"Big List Object","answer_c":"Binary List Object","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":"Binary List Obsolete Object","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":366,"question":"The GROUP BY command cannot be used with aggregate functions together","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":397,"question":"Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"English","answer_b":"The Structured Query Language","answer_c":"Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages","answer_d":"Swedish","answer_e":"Binary","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":328,"question":"Which of the following statements are true?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_b":"Alias names can be up to 255 characters in length","answer_c":"Names of databases, tables and columns can be up to 256 characters in length","answer_d":"Alias names can be up to 64 characters in length","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":246,"question":"What is the name of the utility used to extract NDB configuration information?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ndb_config","answer_b":"cluster_config","answer_c":"ndb --config","answer_d":"configNdb","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":383,"question":"What will be the effect of the query SELECT c.*,e.* FROM clients c INNER JOIN employees e ON c.emp_no = e.emp_no;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"return all the records from the clients table and only those that match the emp_no from the employees table","answer_b":"The query will generate an error","answer_c":"return all the records from the employees table and only those that match the emp_no from the clients table","answer_d":"return only records that have matching emp_no values in both tables","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":395,"question":"The main MySQL program that does all the data handling is called","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Mysql","answer_b":"Mysqld","answer_c":"Httpd","answer_d":"Mysql.exe","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":335,"question":"Which of the following is not a SQL operator?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Between .. and ..","answer_b":"Like","answer_c":"In","answer_d":"Is null","answer_e":"Not in","answer_f":"All of the above are valid SQL operators"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":325,"question":"What will happen if two tables have names 'users' and 'USERS'?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"This is not possible because table names are case insensitive","answer_b":"This depends on lower_case_table_names system variable","answer_c":"This is possible only on UNIX\/LINUX","answer_d":"This is possible only on Windows","answer_e":"This is possible because table names are case sensitive","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":238,"question":"Which of the following is the best MySQL data type for currency values?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SMALLINT","answer_b":"DECIMAL(18,4)","answer_c":"VARCHAR(32)","answer_d":"BIGINT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},
  {"id":559,"question":"Type Hinting was introduced in which version of PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"PHP 5","answer_b":"PHP 6","answer_c":"PHP 4","answer_d":"PHP 7","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":178,"question":"Which command is used to build a Docker image?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker built username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_b":"docker image -t create username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_c":"docker build -t username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_d":"docker create username\/repository_name:1.0.1","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":780,"question":"Which of the mentioned are valid PHP loops","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"for","answer_b":"while","answer_c":"do ... while","answer_d":"foreach","answer_e":"each","answer_f":"beforeeach"},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":300,"question":"What is the difference between character 23 and x23?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"23 specifies the octal 23 and x23 determine the hex 23.","answer_b":"23 specifies the hex 23 and x23 determine the octal 23","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":18,"question":"Which is the best tool to use for logging in remotely?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"rsh","answer_b":"ssh","answer_c":"telnet","answer_d":"login","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":694,"question":"Which command can be used to rename a file\/directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mv","answer_b":"cp","answer_c":"rename","answer_d":"rm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":573,"question":"Which of the following is not true?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"PHP can be used to develop web applications.","answer_b":"PHP can not be embedded into html.","answer_c":"PHP applications can not be compiled","answer_d":"PHP makes a website dynamic","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":536,"question":"HTML documents are saved in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Special binary format","answer_b":"Machine language codes","answer_c":"ASCII text","answer_d":"None of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":207,"question":"DISTINCT keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"There is no such keyword","answer_b":"For selecting only unique records by a specific field","answer_c":"To reduce the load on the server with loss of query performance","answer_d":"To speed up the selection for a specific field","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":549,"question":"Is PHP case sensitive","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Depending on the PHP version either Yes and No","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":706,"question":"What is the purpose of \u2018at\u2019 command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To execute a command\/commands at a specific time.","answer_b":"To execute a command\/commands at a specific request.","answer_c":"To execute a command\/commands on a specific condition.","answer_d":"To execute a command\/commands only when the user has logged in.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":93,"question":"Which of the following is used to set cookies?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"setcookie() function","answer_b":"$_COOKIE variable","answer_c":"$HTTP_COOKIE_VARS variable","answer_d":"isset() function","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":265,"question":"Where is WordPress content stored?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress stores it's content in a MySQL database on the server.","answer_b":"WordPress stores it's content in the wp-content folder","answer_c":"WordPress stores it's content in a MySQL database on the server.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1021,"question":"What Is K8s?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kubernetes, also sometimes called K8S (K \u2013 eight characters \u2013 S), is an open source backend framework for containerized applications that was born from the Azure data centers.","answer_b":"Kubernetes, also sometimes called K8S (K \u2013 eight characters \u2013 S), is an open source orchestration framework for containerized applications that was born from the Google data centers.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":873,"question":"A Docker image provides a template for a container with all the necessary files of an application, but has no instructions to run it.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":329,"question":"How can you change table sctructure after it was created?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE TABLE","answer_b":"MODIFY TABLE","answer_c":"ALTER TABLE","answer_d":"UPDATE TABLE","answer_e":"It's not possible to change the structure","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1030,"question":"How to list all nodes in your Docker swarm?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker node get","answer_b":"docker node print","answer_c":"docker node get-all","answer_d":"docker node ls","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":782,"question":"What does the include() function does?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The include() function takes all the text in a specified file and copies it into the file that uses the include function","answer_b":"The include() function takes the included file and makes sure it's executed before the file the function is used into","answer_c":"The include() function takes specified strings and includes them into another string. This is used when we want to concatenate different strings.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":952,"question":"What are the functions of Replication controller?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It is responsible to control and administer the lifecycle of the pod.","answer_b":"It helps the user to check the running status of the pod","answer_c":"It is responsible to monitor and verify whether the allowed number of pod replicas were running","answer_d":"It is responsible for routing the ingress traffic","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":736,"question":"How to scale a replicaset named 'foo' to 3?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl scale --replicas=3 rs\/foo","answer_b":"kubectl up --replicas=3 rs\/foo","answer_c":"kubectl update --replicas=3 rs\/foo","answer_d":"kubectl deploy  --replicas=3 rs\/foo","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Hard"},

]

console.log(arr.length);


function sortArr(){
  return new Promise((resolve, reject) =>{
    let result = arr.sort(function(a, b) {
      if (a.id > b.id) return 1;
      if (a.id < b.id) return -1;
      return 0;
    });
    resolve(result)
  })
}


let newArr = []

sortArr()
.then((list) => {
  newArr = list
  return newArr
})
.then(list => {
  const fs = require("fs");

  // 書き込むデータ準備
  const data = JSON.stringify(list);

  // 書き込み
  fs.writeFile("file1.sql", data, (err) => {
    if (err) throw err;
    console.log('正常に書き込みが完了しました');
  });
})






